I'm sorry.
Who are you?
The sorcerer who erected
the barrier here.
This spot has been chosen
for people to kill each other in.
Unfortunately,
there's no real honor in it.
Kill each other?
Could you not do that in
my neighborhood, please?
You're funny.
There's an old execution
site not far from here.
That serves as the center of the barrier.
It covers a five- or six-kilometer radius.
I went through great pains
to create this barrier,
so I can't impose restrictions
that are too unreasonable.
Those of you who were inside the barrier
from the start have the right to leave it.
Just once.
If you wish, you could wake
up outside the barrier.
Would you like to?
Wake up?
Is this a dream?
You're in the space between
dreams and reality.
It's a curse.
Be careful.
Take it slowly.
The hasty ones are already outside.
Oh, right.
I nearly forgot to mention it.
Thank you for being friends with my son.
Sasaki!
Iguchi!
I'm so glad to see someone I know.
My legs hurt...
My glasses are missing...
Where are we?
Somewhere between Kotodai
and Hirose Street.
More importantly, look.
What's your opinion on that?
As an occult club member?
On that?
November 1, 06:02, Sendai Colony
Can I talk about a dream?
Everyone's had it.
There was a guy with long
hair and a kasaya, right?
Then did he say something
about his son to you, too?
Oh? No, first time hearing about that.
Itadori?
Episode 54
Tokyo No. 1 Colony, Part 1
JUJUTSU KAISEN
The Culling Game Part 1
For real?
Gojo-san got sealed?
For real.
Damn!
Also, sorry to mention this as an aside,
but the principal's dead, too.
Panda-senpai?
Sorry for not telling you, but it's true.
It's all right, Itadori.
He didn't die in Shibuya.
He fought with the higher-ups after that.
That doesn't make it any better.
The principal was your...
I'm including that in "it's all right."
Thanks, though.
If you say so, then there's
nothing more for us to add.
Yeah.
Still, that's everyone who's
been good to me all at once...
I haven't been this bummed out
since I watched Yakul get shot
in the ass with an arrow.
What a nice life you've lived.
All right. I'll help you all
stop this Culling Game.
Don't get me wrong, though.
I'm not doing this out of sympathy.
We're cutting a deal.
Got me?
Once we clean up this Culling Game,
it's your turn to help me.
You're trying to get in on the revisions
to the Jujutsu Regulations, right?
Now that the existence of
curses has gone public,
there's sure to be some kind of revision,
but what exactly are you hoping for?
Whatever it is, I doubt it'll
be that hard to secure.
Huh?!
What would you know about it,
Sea Urchin Head?! Huh?!
I'm the head of the Zen'in Clan.
Screw it,
I'll use it where I can.
Oh, yeah?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, for real?!
I'm sorry for the other two,
but that's the most shocking
thing I've learned today!
If I got the backing of one
of the big three families,
I could easily influence the
revisions to the regulations.
The only problem would come later,
in trying to keep the Zen'in Clan from
getting involved in managing
the fight club.
Sea Urchin Head!
It's Fushiguro.
Fushiguro-kun!
Let's be friends?
Sure.
The Next Day,
The Zen'in Clan Is Exterminated
Good. That just leaves deciding
who's heading to which Colony.
Yuta went to Miyagi, right?
Ding-dong, ding-dong, ding-dong,
ding-dong, ding-dong, ding-dong!
A Player has added a new
Rule to the Culling Game!
Rule 9: Players shall be able to view the
following information on other players:
8: Players who do not show a
change in points within 19 days of
joining or acquiring points
shall be stripped of their technique.
9: Players shall be able to view the
following information on other players:
name, points, number of
rules added, current Colony.
rules added, current colony.
I am Kogane!
A liaison between Players
and the Culling Game!
Did that thing just change
personality midway through?
The first part was an announcement
from the Culling Game!
Now I'm speaking as the personal liaison
attached to the Player Itadori Yuji!
Tengen-sama did mention
something about that.
Wait, this still isn't right!
Why would Itadori be counted
as a Player already?
Aside from those Kenjaku gave cursed
techniques or cursed objects,
the only Players should be
those who have entered a Colony!
One type was people whom I had absorb
cursed objects like Yuji Itadori did...
The cursed objects that I distributed
are what's left of the sorcerers
I've been secretly making
pacts for a thousand years.
Of course, I forged my pacts with
more than just sorcerers...
He's actually a human who really existed,
though it was over a thousand years ago.
Sukuna.
Sukuna?
I think Sukuna was one of the sorcerers
who forged a pact with Kenjaku
and became a cursed object.
Is participation in the Culling Game
included in their pact, then?
That's still strange, though.
You swallowed Sukuna's finger
of your own free will.
I witnessed it.
We'll save that for later.
Itadori, could you have Kogane pull up
the Players' information right now?
Kogane, can you?
Sure can!
Ta-da!
This guy.
So this guy originally had 200 points?
I wonder what he was hoping
for by adding a rule.
At the very least,
he's killed 40 people, right?
So it's not going to be a
very nice reason, yeah?
Still, this means
we might be able to progress through the
Culling Game without killing anyone.
Kogane, can you show a list of just
the players with 100 points or more?
I'm attached to Itadori Yuji, so...
Oh, it's fine.
Do what he asked.
Searching
Unless someone who got caught
up in this like Tsumiki did
is in a rush to escape
the barrier, then...
The past sorcerers who have incarnated
also just forged pacts with Kenjaku
for their own reasons,
so they're not necessarily
motivated to do this.
If there's anyone else with an excess
of points like Kashimo...
Right!
People who have over 100 points and
no intention of adding a rule!
We can lean on them...
...and make them add a rule to let
Tsumiki escape the Culling Game!
Here you are.
Searching
Hajime Kashimo
Points
Rule Added
Current Colony: Tokyo No. 2
Hiromi Higuruma
Points
Rules Added
Current Colony: Tokyo No. 1
There's another one!
Yeah!
First, we'll have to take advantage
of the obstacle Rule 8 poses.
Huh?
What was Rule 8 again?
8: Players who do not show a
change in points within 19 days
of joining or acquiring points
shall be stripped of their technique.
Players who do not show a change
in points within 19 days
Day
shall be stripped of their technique.
It's the Rule that leads to death.
So we add a Rule that says,
"It is possible for Players to
transfer points among each other."
That way, if they keep passing
points between each other,
they can avoid being stripped
of their techniques and dying.
Then, if possible, we add one more.
"Players may expend
points to leave the Culling Game."
We add a Rule like, "Players may expend
Wouldn't that conflict with the Rule
about the continuation of the game?
I think it would, too.
But we might be able to get around
that by adding a condition
like dragging a non-Player into the
Culling Game to take their place.
True.
Would Kogane be making the call on that?
Either way, we know what
we need to do now.
Yeah.
Angel
While we're searching for the Angel
to break the Prison Realm's seal,
we'll pursue Hajime Kashimo
and Hiromi Higuruma,
and hunt them down.
Persuade Players with 100 Points
and No Intention of Adding a Rule
Hunt Down Hajime Kashimo
Hunt Down Hiromi Higuruma
Yeah, there's seriously no "Angel" on here.
That probably isn't her real name.
Just like you're not listed as Sukuna.
Tengen-sama said she was
in eastern Tokyo...
That would be Colony No. 2, then.
You guys know what she looks like?
Apparently, we'll know when see her.
Is that gonna work out?
Well, whatever.
Panda and I will take Tokyo No. 2.
Fushiguro-kyun and Itadori can take No. 1.
Kirara, stand by outside the barriers.
Huh?
Sound good?
What's your reasoning?
Just going by points,
this Kashimo's the strongest one,
so it makes sense for me to take him.
I'm being excluded?
You've got a keen nose, Panda,
so focus on finding the Angel.
The fact that we haven't
already heard from Okkotsu
means we probably can't use cell
phones inside the barriers.
So we'll want someone to keep tabs
on what's going on outside them.
Fine.
Wait.
It might be best for me and
Fushiguro to be split up.
Sukuna is—
Shut up.
"Shut up"?!
Our three senpai can't
change their roles.
So quit being selfish.
Selfish?!
I'm just worrying about you here!
Are you going to say that every time?
What a pain. Such a waste of time.
Huh?!
Don't fight.
November 11th 12:00 Tokyo
(Remaining Time Until Tsumiki
Must Enter the Culling Game:
7 Days 12 Hours)
Hey, I'm Kogane!
Inside this barrier is the Culling Game,
where Players fight to the death!
Once you step inside,
you, too, become a Player!
Are you still willing to enter?!
Yeah!
Yeah.
No issues here.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Hey, Amai!
I keep waiting for your signal!
Uh, well, I hear you,
but there's nothing I can
do if no one's showing up.
Huh?
Are you mouthing off to me now?
No! Look, I'm sorry!
Please forgive me!
If you get too uppity,
I'll run you over.
We need to be wary of the past
sorcerers who incarnated.
My thoughts, too.
But explain it to me
again, Fushiguro-kun.
Some of them are from
a thousand years ago.
Yet the value of a life was way different
even a hundred or two hundred years ago.
Plus, they're sorcerers.
Fighting and death are common for them.
Some may want to die fighting.
That might even be why they
forged a pact with Kenjaku.
There's a strong chance that Higuruma
and Kashimo are past sorcerers.
Don't expect a proper negotiation.
Then the other aggressive ones are
going to be cursed spirits, huh?
Especially at night.
If they're a modern day sorcerer
dragged into this like Tsumiki,
they actually might be open
to exchanging information.
Hey, I'm Kogane!
Inside this barrier is the Culling Game,
where Players fight to the death!
Once you step inside,
you, too, become a Player!
Are you still willing to enter?!
Yeah, no issues here.
Megumi Fushiguro has
joined the Culling Game.
Would you like to see the Rules?
No need. I'm fine.
Boo.
Boo...
Itadori.
Huh?
First, we gather information on Higuruma.
Let's go.
Yeah!
Fushiguro's gone?!
When a Player enters one of
the Culling Game's barriers,
they're randomly teleported to one
of nine designated locations.
It was a rule of the barriers not included
in the general rules of the Culling Game.
But they were waiting in
those nine locations...
Here's one!
Players who targeted those disoriented
by this unmentioned phenomenon.
Newbie-hunters.
He's tough!
This would have turned
most into mincemeat.
But he's still kicking.
He's no ordinary person.
Darling, let's meet up.
She fell easily.
I need to ask her about Higuruma.
Then I have to find Fushiguro.
What the hell?!
What did you do to my woman?!
Guess I can just ask him.
Haba-san flew in.
Was Hanyu-san taken out?
I've seen him before...
Itadori?!
Ow! That hurts!
Why are you doing this?!
You're the one who attacked me.
Damn it!
I didn't expect us to
get separated that way.
Well?
Nue can't find him, either.
This Colony must be much
larger than Shibuya.
We're probably over two kilometers apart.
But we both know where to head.
Do you know a sorcerer named Higuruma?
Men think they can just beat women
into listening to them, don't they?
Answer me!
Yes. I'm sorry.
By Higuruma, you mean that guy, right?
The one with 100 points?
Do you know where he is?
I see. So that's how it is.
Damn brat!
What physical prowess!
I thought I'd be in trouble with him
constantly holding higher ground,
but that propeller's his
only means of attack.
He keeps coming in close
to try to kill me.
I'll fight him indoors!
I'll turn you into a smoothie!
He's turned his head toward me!
That earlier airplane woman
was sturdy enough to smash
through buildings with me,
but she fell from such
a simple thrown object.
Their hair is the core
of their technique,
so they're probably less sturdy the
further away from their hair you get.
Because of a pact?
But no matter how tough it may be,
it's still their head.
As long as I can attack it,
I can crack it open!
Broke your fist, did ya?
You just lost this battle!
I didn't break anything. Ow.
I don't mind telling you,
but I want you to do me a favor in return.
Spit it out.
Say it, pl...?
Tell me, pl...?
Say it.
Fine.
Become my knight?
Sure. That's fine.
Am I that much of a bore?
I just don't have time.
Hurry it up.
Walk in front.
Do you even get it?!
My knight is supposed to
protect me with his life!
I will if you're telling me the truth.
Hey, wake up.
I want to ask you about a
sorcerer named Higuruma.
I-Itadori.
I know him.
That Higuruma guy.
You know what will happen
if you're lying, right?
I'm not like Itadori.
I'm willing to earn those
100 points on my own.
Split Ahead
Stop calling me "you."
My name is Remi.
It's been a long time.
Do you remember me?
Who are you?
How does he know my name?
Oh, sorry.
I guess it was just me
who knew about you.
You were famous, you know.
The Tiger of West Middle School.
Oh! You're from my hometown!
Split Ahead
What, you're not a
sorcerer from the past?
Huh? Do I look that far behind the times?
What's your reason for taking
the initiative to fight, then?
Listen, you.
Average people who weren't Players
got let out of the Colony,
but us Players who were in
the Colony from the start
have had to participate in the
Culling Game for twelve days already!
Split Ahead
I'm not doing this because I want to!
It's kill or be killed!
You'll get killed while you're trying
to find your reason to fight.
Anyone can figure that out
after twelve days here.
I've seen plenty of people drown
in their power during that time.
So stop trying to differentiate between
them as past or present sorcerers.
So the past sorcerers have inspired
even the modern-day sorcerers
to go into battle mode.
I might have given Itadori
bad advice, then.
Are you sure? You were allies, right?
With those two?
I was just their gofer.
They would have killed me at some point.
Wait.
Tell me where we're going already.
Look!
There's no guarantee that you won't
kill me after I tell you, right?
I see. Uh...
Amai.
It's Rin Amai.
What am I supposed to do if
you die before I get there?
That's why! You need to! Protect me!
And use my name already!
Anything could happen.
Amai, where is Higuruma?
Well, fine.
I'll give you a rough idea.
The stronger people are gathered
where the city once thrived.
Since resources are in good supply there.
Higuruma is in...
...Ikebukuro.
...Shinjuku.
Got it?
I just sense potential
in the Culling Game.
Every person in this nation will die.
She deceived you.
I'm sorry, Itadori.
A sorcerer connected to Kenjaku?!
I want to talk.
Next Episode
Tokyo No. 1 Colony, Part 2
We're having a retrial.